Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.MY-SUBS.org today
You know what you're milking it.
Besides, I think we got it.
I think we got it.
We got it.
We got it up there.
Thank you, Yakityak.
You laid it all out beautifully.
If I frame Blionheart, I can frame you too.
It's my word against yours.
Actually, and I'll dart every predator in Zootopia to keep it that way.
It's your word against yours.
It's called a hustle, sweetheart.
Boom.
Unlikely duo, Judy Hawks, the city's first bunny cop, and Nicholas Wilde, a small-time street fox, uncovered a conspiracy by Mayor Bellwether today using a toy carrot recorder pen.
I can frame you too.
Wilde later joined the ZPD himself, where the pair are now the very first bunny fox team in the history of Zootopia.
New mayor and former actor Brian Windancer hailed the two during celebrations for the 100th anniversary of the invention of Zootopia's weather walls that allowed all environments and all animals to coexist in one city.
This is our Zootenium.
And if a lonely country bunny and a shifty, likely criminal fox could ignore their vast, past differences and solve bias and stereotype forever, then maybe we can all embrace our differences and be better together.
We're gonna crack a new case, make the world a better place, and be the greatest partners of all time.
I mean, we're not that different.
At the ZPD, partnership is the cornerstone of success.
You want to put bad guys away?
Be on the same page every day.
Now, today's bad guy is this customs inspector who's been smuggling legal overseas cargo through the city's shipyard.
Captains Hogbottom and Truffler will lead.
Higgins, Bloats, flank, left.
Chevra, Ushron, right, and down the middle, the Zebros.
Zebros?
Hops and Wild?
I know you're eager to prove yourselves, but as rookies, you will observe only and watch the veteran teams show you how it...
Chief, hi.
If you're looking for Nick and Judy, they said they got it, and they're already on site with their baby.
Are you sure this will work?
You're the one that said we needed a bust.
Just follow my lead, okay?
Act casual.
Hey, here we go.
Hello!
This whole area is restricted.
You can't be here.
Whoa, fox and bunny.
Okay.
Yes, but proud parents first.
Mr.
Inspector.
Inspector Snootley.
Inspector?
What do you do?
Ensure that nothing illegal gets smuggled here in one of these cargo containers?
That's a weird way to ask that.
Anyway, you gotta leave.
You can't be here.
Wait.
He's right, gosh darn it.
You are right, sir.
I guess we should have thought this through, right, babe?
Before we decided to come down here to this beautiful industrial shipyard to celebrate the big day of our birthday, boy.
It's his birthday?
Yeah, first one since...
since the accident.
And you know the one thing this little stinker wished for, aside from one day getting his tail reattached, was to see a choo-choo.
And to maybe get a toot-toot conductor to sign his cast.
But on Betton, a customs inspector would be even better.
Really?
Alright, for the kid.
For the kid.
Oh, you're a saint.
Well, thank you so much.
Here you go.
Either leg.
Or both.
I don't care.
Maybe put a doodle on it.
Doesn't need to be perfect.
He's also legally blind.
I put a little train there because I know you like trains.
Come on, come on, come on.
Just chill.
Yes, I know.
Hurry.
I got this.
Jiggle it, jiggle it, jiggle it.
Ops and wolf!
You are not authorized.
Stand down and wait for a backup!
Toot, toot.
Here's the fun!
Stop!
Stop in the name of the law!
Everybody run!
Well, can't win them all.
Get out of the road, you dumb bunny!
Agree to disagree!
My hog rod!
This is a snail dream!
Huck to the wild in pursuit of suspect and a stolen catering van heading east!
Heading east through Sheepshire!
Beautiful!
I'll have what he's having.
Verlin, I believe you're driving, giving me some white hairs.
Also, am I always going to be in the passenger seat?
Because if we're establishing some real team passwords, ma'am, we are a real team.
I'm gonna jump!
I would like to call a partner meeting.
Please join me in a moment of silence for our beloved Weatherwall inventor, Ebenezer Linksley.
Utopia ain't just a mammal city.
It has a secret tiny reptile population.
The mouth live abroad.
Of course, utopia does not allow snakes.
And he's been one of those around here for at least a hundred years.
Nature Nibbles Naples is our most reliable source.
Sir, today may not have an idea, but the antiater was captured by the zebros!
Zebros!
Got it!
It was us!
But more importantly, I believe we may have made a significant discovery.
The stolen van contained a smuggled crate from overseas, pamphlets for the zutenial, and some type of reptile skin.
I've already sent samples for testing.
And what needs testing is you!
You two tore up half the city!
Because of you, we had to call it in jumbo unit to remove a tick dick from a tuba!
You're almost out!
Sorry, could you show me that clip again?
I wasn't wearing my glasses.
Did you or did you not disobey a direct order to stand down?
Sir, we were in pursuit.
And Article 6, paragraph B, states: if the lead officers are not lead officers, you're one-hit wonders who should go back to meter-mating and slinging popsicles.
If I may, I think someone's just jealous that we got to drive the squeal mobile.
Or maybe you thought it was your mama.
Enough!
Everybody!
Out!
Officer Hobbs, despite my best efforts to avoid it, I like you.
But this need to overdo it made both of you a headline today.
And it reflects badly on me, on the department, and frankly, on anybody hoping to follow in your footsteps.
Not every case is going to save the world.
Knock, knock.
Hi.
You know, it's kind of...
This sounds a lot like just a you guys conversation, so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna go.
Is there a reason why you don't take anything seriously?
Jokes are a classic defense mechanism for someone with a traumatic childhood.
Would you like a traumatic adulthood?
I would not.
I allowed you to work together because you did this city a great service, but today you messed it all up.
And now, some are questioning whether you should have been partners in the first place.
So, instead of chasing imaginary reptiles, I am pulling you from the field and giving you a new assignment reserved for special teams like yourselves.
Fail at this, and I will have no choice but to split you up.
There will be no more hops and wild.
But if you're as good as you think you are, this is your moment to shine.
Welcome to Partners in Crisis, a workshop for duos heading for disaster.
I'm your therapy animal, Dr.
Fuzbee, and you are here because mismatched pairings often need a little more work to make them work.
Greg?
We talked about that.
What are we making Marlon?
Uncomfortable.
Yes.
And Francine, Clark may be a mouse, but he is your partner first.
And we have two new partners.
Can you tell us about your journey to Dysfunction Junction?
Well, we've been official partners for one week, happy anniversary.
And we are not dysfunctional at all, actually.
Functioning fine, better than fine.
And we did sort of save the city.
So us being here kind of seems like a huge misunderstanding.
Notice how she answered first, did not allow her partner to speak, seems to be in a state of denial, and taps her foot when she's suppressing discomfort.
And observe the source of her discomfort, represented by the disconnected affectation of her emotionally insecure partner.
But with hard work, they'll be on the same page by year two.
But for now, let's begin by greeting our teammate.
Who'd like to go first?
Thank you, Joel.
Okay, unfortunately, Karen has chosen to see Joel's smile as a sign of aggression.
Heckles down, Karen.
Karen!
Heckles down!
Joel, the safe word is coconut!
Okay, we have to set another meeting with the chief.
Promise we'll be better.
You talk back less.
Maybe not at all.
Yeah, or we go with my playbook and we just lay low.
We cannot prove ourselves if we are stuck in that room.
And if we complain to Chief Beef, he'll just make us stay longer.
It's smart, stay off the radar, and don't let it get to you, okay?
Because we are the dream team.
Sorry, Paul.
Oh, roll out the red carpet.
Here's the super cops.
Wait, what does the fox say?
You suck!
Easy, partner.
Let me ask you something.
Do you think we're a good team?
Of course.
I just...
I just wish I knew what we had to do to prove it to everyone else.
Or maybe we don't have to prove anything to anybody.
We do.
Forever.
Woof!
And the sooner everyone sees a fox and a bunny can be great partners, the better.
Enjoy it.
I got to.
I'd rather chew off my own arm.
Happy anniversary!
So, saw you on TV.
You okay?
Everything's fine, Mom.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, everyone knows fine is a cry for help.
You know who else cried for help?
That dick dick stuck in that tuba.
What does your fox partner say?
Well, Nick's not really a talker.
Well, you two are very different.
Small-town hero raised on a farm.
Big city crook raised on the streets.
I pray every day that you'll come back home and make babies.
Just remember the first rule of partnerships.
You can be right, or you can be happy.
That's true.
There's nothing wrong with dying a little inside so you can meet in the middle.
Honey, you're pushing me out.
I want to make sure I can be seen.
Well, if she could see both of us.
Bye, Bunbun.
Everything's going to be fine.
You two just need a new case.
Maybe try to find that dictator.
Bye.
Tomorrow's weather is, again, everything to announce that the long-awaited Tundertown expansion will be starting soon.
Residents continue to raise concerns about the future of their neighborhood.
But tonight, we put our differences aside and celebrate at the Zootennial Gala, where the Linksley Journal will be on display for the first time in a century, following an infamous reptile attack.
The Linksley Journal, containing the patented weather wall plans, was originally written by Ebenezer Linksley, bringing the whole carrying company.
The Linksley Journal.
Truth Bomb!
The 100th anniversary of the Weather Walls is also the 100th anniversary of Zootopia's only snake attack.
The victim?
A tortoise.
The Linksley family maid, who is fanged while stopping a venomous snake from stealing the Linksley Journal.
No one has seen a snake in Zootopia since, but I'm convinced one will return.
My only question is, is he gonna be wearing half a pants or one long sock?
You say justice is dead.
I say well, well, you missed me already, huh?
The stolen van with the snake skin is from the same catering company that's working the gala.
Mm-hmm.
This is you studying your partner book.
Listen to me.
Venomous snakes tried to steal the Linksley's journal before.
What if they're back in town to steal it again?
No snake has set foot in Zootopia in forever.
Okay, even if they had feet.
Look, we're already in the hot seat, Carrots.
Aunt Pizza's here.
Gotta go.
If there's a fanging at the gala and we do nothing to stop it, then we are not doing our job.
Zikes.
No wonder you never invite me over.
Foxes are solitary.
We go and you're wrong.
Chief Beef will split us up.
And if we don't get a win soon and prove we're great partners, the chief will split us up anyway.
Check the perimeter, snoop a little.
We find nothing, we bail.
But if I'm right, no one will question whether you and I belong together again.
We need this.
Fine, but we'll still have to get through security, and in Fancy Town, a fox and a bunny won't exactly blend in.
That's why we'll be undercover!
See, you're still in the driver's seat.
Come on, get on up!
We're wild out, we can't be tipped.
And we're turning the floor into a drug.
When we begin with 200 times, someone does it.
No snow.
This one's warmer.
Reptile in Tundra town might need that to survive the cold.
Oh my god, a viper!
A window viper.
Yeah?
Anyone could have left it like that.
And you said simple it, not breaking anything.
We were always going inside, got it.
Same page means your page.
It's called a hustle, sweetheart.
You can't get your packet.
You know, this is not your worst idea.
Wow, that was almost a compliment.
Your worst idea is what you did with your ears.
Boom!
Welcome to the Zutennial Gallery, featuring the original Linksley Journal.
Why would a snake want to steal some old book, anyway?
I don't know.
But no one is going to steal it because we are here to protect it.
Hmm.
The journal is in the reserved section.
Okay.
No.
Come on.
Slow down.
You want to fit in?
Commando is not going to cut it.
It's not just the clothes, okay?
It is the vibe.
Good to see ya.
Hey, real nice humps.
Oh, is that real Mink?
This real fox?
Get invited to a lot of these.
Invited?
No, but there's other reasons to hobnob.
Madam, excuse me, is this yours?
Why, yes.
Well, allow me.
Clever fox.
There!
I don't think it has enough guards.
Okay, closer look.
Watch my sex.
The cover is made of metal.
Gruffalo Buffalo has joined the mix.
Three o'clock.
Oh, excuse me.
Oh, no.
Sorry.
God, here, let me just.
Oh, nope.
That belongs to you.
I apologize.
Oh, God, he hates me.
Here.
You're my hero.
Well, just like to be prepared for any possible scenario.
Which is not a weird thing to say to party.
Well, I just mopped a spill with that guy's tail, so.
Haw!
Uh, Hubbert!
I am Hubbert!
Hi!
Judy, I'm Judy Hopps.
Ah!
What the pork?
Well, it is nice to meet you, Judy.
Wait, Judy Hopps, the Judy Hopps?
Are you working this?
I mean, you're clearly working it.
But are you actually working this?
Uh, no, I'm actually, well, it's just a hunch protecting that.
Good.
I don't think it has enough guards.
That was my joke.
And there's nothing here.
Let's call it a night.
Hopps?
Well, we should.
It was nice to meet you.
Yes, and you.
Bonapetite.
If at any point tonight you choose to eat, Bonapet then.
You're supposed to be off stage, Pobert.
Yeah, get off stage, Pobert.
We are.
Are you?
Yeah, I am a Linksley.
Or, you know, I'm trying to be.
Now, Pobert.
Come on, Poppy.
I got you, Pot.
I have them.
All right, let's get this thing started.
Welcome to the Zutennial Gala.
Hey, Hops.
I think I might actually...
I think I've got something.
Ah, look at you all.
Good to see you.
It is with great pleasure that I introduce the third generation.
Garrots!
Can you hear me?
I have a trail.
Thank you, thank you.
What are you doing?
She was right.
You're done.
You're both done.
My grandpa.
Please, you don't have to hurt him.
Hurt him?
Snakes never hurt anyone.
We aren't the bad guys.
They are.
And this journey holds the secret that will prove it.
I have to prove it.
Please.
This is our only chance to set things right.
And when I do, my family will finally be able to come home.
Woo!
I am here.
Cops and wilds.
Dream team.
We got him.
Or her.
And reptiles.
It's like, who knows?
The cops are right behind us.
Kill the snake.
We'll burn the journal.
If he wants it, it's dangerous..
And you two will file a report that he attacked us.
And you will keep your mouth shut.
Step aside.
Put out the fire!
Here it is!
Help me, save them!
Here it is, we are!
We're helping the snake!
We're trying to kill the kids!
Next time, we'll stay home.
No!
Stop!
I really am just a dumb buddy!
Accident, your words, not mine.
Put him in the trunk.
Terroar in Tundra Town!
Fanging at the fiesta!
Hooooo!
Lapping Gala!
As a venomous snake attacks the founding family.
More shocking, the snake was aided by embattled ZPD officers Nicholas Wilde and Judy Hupps.
All three now suspects in the tragic fanging of Zootopia's chief of police and considered extremely dangerous.
Chief Bogo is dead.
Those are words I'm glad I don't have to say.
I might have to, son.
The doctor's a little worded out, but what has happened tonight was more than horseplay.
And the fox!
And that rabbit!
Do you know how many mayors they've already destroyed?
I got up to two.
Would you like to be three?
I want them gone.
But aren't they blazed?
I will say this once, Brian.
You will retrieve the journal and bury them.
Or maybe I chose the wrong mayor.
Did I choose the wrong mayor?
Hey, the phone is the first thing I'll try.
Sorry, I have never been on the run from the law before.
Yeah, boy, it's almost like we shouldn't have gone to that gala.
Huh?
Okie-doke, we already did it your way.
With Mr.
Big, we do it mine.
This is where having a partner from the underworld is really going to pay off.
Raymond, and is that Kevin?
Welcome to my warehouse.
Oh my god, I love your dress.
Oh, thank you.
Prufreu and I are now equal partners in the family business.
She brings wonderful ideas for crime and for fashion.
While I get more time to focus on what matters most.
Being grandpapa to my little Judith.
Yes, my mean.
Just think of me right now.
Just no, no, you said we were gonna make cement shoes for Miss Lisa Kirk.
Oh, that's the girl.
They grew up so fast.
You run your mouth too much.
Fox!
Anyways, you're in trouble.
And we like one of yous.
So, we're here to help.
New clothes, new identities, truck out of town, leave it at all.
And you mean a maid card is taken care of.
I think you misunderstand.
We've been framed by the lynxes and an innocent city.
Really?
The lynxes are killers.
And they have no honor.
And this Tundra Town expansion only makes them more dangerous.
Territorial animals will do anything for more land.
So if whatever you're tangled up in threatens their plans, you're dead.
You don't fight the cats.
You leave.
Sir, I know you're trying to look out for us, but we took an oath to protect this city, and justice doesn't run.
On behalf of myself, Rick Wilde, and Miss Trudy Cabbage Patch, we thank you for your truck to salvation.
Thank you.
I cannot accept your offer.
We are helping that snake.
Boy, you're really tossing that wee around.
Snakes may have been framed for the fanging of that tortoise.
Do you have any idea why?
Or how this book could prove it?
I wish I did.
But if it has to do with snakes, your best bet is talking to a reptile.
Do you know any?
Almost no one does.
They keep to themselves.
Hide out in marsh market.
But you can still find them.
You just need a reptile expert.
Someone local who knows where to go.
Lucky for you, I met someone.
She runs the park next.
No, no.
Trudy Cabbage Patch.
Rick Wild says no.
Oh, yeah.
Hops and wild are on the land.
Sudden sleuth and tismy.
Gam!
Woo!
Mine splinters.
Oh, you call the right beaver.
If you want to talk to a reptile, I am your gal.
Also, if you need to talk to a jackalope, which are real, mom.
Excuse us.
Team meeting.
Vetoing the beeve.
New vote, all in favor of truck to being alive and laying low till this blows over, Ville?
I mean.
Hups and wild do not pale on a case.
Which is crazy.
Probably lead poisoning from getting too many pencils.
Do you know a reptile who can tell us the hidden secret in here or why the links is framed the snakes?
24 hours, sunrise tomorrow.
If we strike out, then we go into hiding in Judy Cabbage Patch.
It is.
It's Trudy Cabbage Patch, and the safe word is coconut.
In the darkness of a dank underpass, they stepped into the vehicle, not realizing their lives were about to change.
Because we're gonna meet a reptile?
Because you're about to be best buds with Nibbles Maple Street!
Takes two to tango, but a threesome to be some.
Let's find a reptile and rough the swamp.
Now a pretty reptile would know the secret of that book and why the snake wants it.
Hey, Johnny!
It's my old lizard friend, Jesus.
Why would a lizard hide here?
Well, when Zootopia was founded, the whole neighborhood got cut off from the rest of the town.
Kind of on our own here.
Yeah, that's probably why reptiles like it.
They can just do their thing.
Plus, it's the only place in town you can get away with wearing a shirt and no pants.
Loving to her time with wood chuckles.
Great girl.
We need her.
Oh, yeah.
Like a hole in the head.
Bad timing.
Okay, to get to Jesus' hideout, you gotta take a ferry.
Just let me handle the locals.
Water folk tend to be a little standoffish around Landy's.
Well, I've been hustling the streets since I was 12.
Think I can handle a juggling seal.
Oh!
Sea lion.
He's not from around here.
But coin's a coin.
Oh, no, change is a choking hazard.
Well, honest mistake.
Do not do that.
Let's let Nivills handle this.
Thank you, Judith.
Conversing with these beautiful sea creatures is like talking to anyone a little different.
Just takes open and respectful communicative fellowship.
Hey, Bub.
Hey, Abub.
Hey, Abuba.
Hey, hey, Bub, hey.
Hey, Abub.
Hey, Bub, hey, Bub, Bubba.
Hey, Bub, Bubby, Bub.
Hey, Bubb, hey, Bubby, Bub.
Hey, Bub.
Sine Zeus.
Yup.
And now we leave town.
Thank you for this.
Happy anniversary.
Oh, it's your anniversary.
This is the night.
It's a beautiful night.
And we know the light.
How are we gonna find them now?
Thanks, Seal.
Just a little farther.
Hey, Seuss, and all the answers you'll ever need are right here at the end of this very scary, dark hallway.
Boy, this is so much better than sitting on a beach on Albac Island, sipping piña koalas.
We are not skipping town when there is an innocent snake out there who needs us.
He's got help.
His motorcycle buddy.
You are acting weird.
What is your problem?
Well, A, you railroaded me.
And B, if you must know, I have an aversion to reptiles.
What?
Oh, is my discomfort hilarious to you?
No, you're- I'm sorry.
You're right.
We are partners.
And whenever I'm uncomfortable, you are always very considerate of my feelings.
Look at how snakeskin!
I'm slipping.
Hold the rail.
Hold the rail, hold the rail, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it.
I think the real mystery is how you two ever solved anything.
Anywho, let's see what Jesus has to say about your journal.
Oh, and if he offers you food, accept.
Declining is a sign of disrespect to all of them.
All of them?
Order up.
Hey, another drink.
So warm.
Whoops.
No.
Keep it.
Hey, Seuss!
Allow me to introduce my friends.
This is Judith and Nicholas.
They are wanted fugitives investigating a snake mystery and trying not to get murderedered.
May I sit?
Oh, okay.
Oh, I'm good, but these guys look hungry.
Thank you for meeting with us.
We believe snakes were framed for something in this journal.
Perhaps pertaining to.
First, dogs second.
Oh!
Hey, guys!
Look at their faces!
I don't need crumbs.
Hermano, get me a scone.
Okay, okay.
Hmm.
Metal cover.
And what does that mean?
It means it's fancy.
It also means the secret you're looking for is probably right on the cover.
Somehow, vipers can see things in the metal, even under the paint.
This is Ebenezer Linksley's original journal for the weather walls.
Why would he hide a secret for a snake?
I don't know, but it must have been big.
Because a tortoise died for it.
I am guessing that it was a slow death.
The fang didn't just change how folks are snakes.
No mammals trusted any reptile after that.
That's why we all left.
And that's when the Lynx League expanded Tundra Town the first time.
And it's happening again.
The expansion is going here.
Marsh Market will be buried in snow.
We'll all get pushed out.
Those Lynxes will get more land.
And there's no way to stop them.
What if the secret hidden in here could then?
I would say holding it puts the two of you in grave danger.
They trapped you!
It's the ZPD!
Follow me!
Come on!
Wait, why are you helping us?
You two saved the city once.
I reckon you can save it again.
And when you do, maybe everyone will see we ain't that different.
Please!
Yes!
I'm really sorry, but this is my family's only chance to come home.
We want to help!
Oh, wait, wait!
Take the dogs!
Everything you need, I got 'em.
Sequels, prequels, requals.
Who says the industry's going down the dude?
Are you okay?
Yeah, yes.
Uh, you?
Uh, well, I I I feel like some some sorries uh may be in order.
Nick, it's okay.
I know you didn't want to lose him on purpose.
Oh, not me, sorry.
No, no, you sorry.
I have no way to find him or stop the links.
So, agree to disagree.
But we are alive.
So, if we can't find him, that's great.
What we can find is a truck out of here.
Box of old matches.
Helpful.
Turning cabbage patch.
Leaving town.
We're done.
This is the address for you today.
You're very good.
Jersey fell out of the tube.
Okay, give a couple police to help.
No, no, no, we're fine.
Yeah, but we were just leaving town.
Actually, um, do you happen to know where this tube goes?
Oh, Copenhofen.
Yeah, I was Kopenhofen.
Got it.
Jacy.
Oh, you chewed too much.
This is not a where did where did you find these flowers?
Oh, the Leipschen flower?
Is it deep at the top of the mountain?
Uh, this is only Place Embro.
Is uh is there anything else up there?
Nope, there sure isn't.
Oh, yeah, old honeymoon lodge.
What is closed for a long time was hideout for snakes.
Honeymoon lodge?
How how do you reach it?
Oh, Taurus takes the time from Kopenofen, but the rope is faster.
Good luck!
I've funded the honeymoon lodge!
Thank you!
What does this secret have to do with the reptiles leaving down?
How did he get hidden in the jungle in the first place?
Will you slow down?
How long do you think it's gonna be before Hog Bottom and the ZPD figure out where we are?
If anything, we should be going faster.
As I always say, I really am just a dope bunny.
Nick, I really am.
This all was a gift.
to symbolize our partnership.
And it is not appropriate for this moment.
Oh, no, I was just hoping to jot down some ideas for what we will put on our tombstones.
I'll start.
His partner did it.
What happened to you that you can't just have a normal conversation?
I will save that for my therapy animal.
Yeah, you need a therapy animal.
Oh, yeah.
Well, you need a herd of therapy animals.
Yeah, you need a whole migration of therapy animals.
Uh, carrots.
Carrots.
There was a whole reptile neighborhood.
They're home.
The lynxes just erased it.
This is what they do.
We have to go.
They push animals out with lives so they can have more.
We gotta go, Karis, we gotta go.
That's what the snake's trying to prove.
P.D.
is here.
What?
No, he won't believe us.
Not without proof.
Believe it.
They aren't gonna just arrest us.
The lynxes want us dead.
We need to solve the case.
Judy, Judy.
We have to solve the case, Nick.
I don't care about the case.
Judy, it's not worth dying for.
The world will never be a better place if no one is brave enough to do the right thing.
The world is what it is, Carrots, and sometimes being a hero just doesn't make a difference.
I think, uh I think maybe, maybe we are different.
Oh my gosh, I think I just took out a cop.
Sorry, sir!
Hubbard?
It's uh, you know, we're the good guys!
I told you to keep helping.
We have to pop!
We have the puck!
Please!
Here we go!
She's a good one!
You're not dead!
She's not dead!
Sorry, sorry!
I just got my motorcycle license!
Nick they, uh they caught him, but out here, no one's gonna catch us!
Mayor Windan, sir!
Where's the bunny?
I don't know.
But you know, she's a rabbit.
So maybe you can pull her out of your hat.
I'm not wearing a hat.
He's messing with you, sir.
I knew that!
Get him out of here!
Where are they, Mr.
Wild?
Begin the expansion.
Freeze Marsh Market.
Flush everyone out.
Waterfolk, like foxes, or lesser mammals.
If I say they helped a dangerous snake, no one will care what we do.
You're going to a dark cell, Mr.
Wild.
Just long enough to read the headline of your partner's demise.
You should have left town when you had the chance.
Dad.
Fur.
From whoever's helping the bunny and the snake.
Find Popper.
Almost to me hideout.
Snake in the hole.
Yeah, yeah.
We shall succeed, Judy Hops.
We'll stop the linkslings and save your partner.
I'm sorry.
You are...
Oh, Gary.
Gary the Snake.
And your last name?
The Snake.
Everything is going to be okay.
Teaming up with you is very exciting.
Don't worry about my fangs.
I got my own ante villipin.
Stops the toxin.
Stab me straight into the heart.
Welcome to my oasis!
Away from my evil family.
I like to come here, just kind of veg out, get with all my cat stuff.
No!
That's actually vintage.
You could just not.
Oh, no, no, please don't.
Wow, Mamos get him!
No, not that!
Turn it off, turn it off, turn it off, turn it off, turn it off!
So, we should probably get to the journal.
How did you become partners?
Oh, when I found out the journal was going to be on display at the gala, I sent his family an anonymous letter asking to see it.
Luckily, they made Albert work in the mailroom, so he made it first.
I got him smuggled in from overseas.
Seven days in a crate.
But if I fix things for my family, it'll be worth it.
Then you will fix things for your partner, too.
Hey, I know coming with us was hard, but we're gonna help your partner.
The same way we're gonna help the city.
We stop my family and show everyone the truth.
Are you ready?
Fire!
How much do you know?
Well, that his family was framed.
And there's some secret hidden in the metal cover that only a snake can see.
Not just any snake.
A heat-sensing pit viper.
All it takes is a little warmth.
I just.
I don't understand.
Why would your great-grandfather hide a secret for a snake?
He didn't.
I.
It wasn't his journal.
That's the secret.
Zootopia wasn't created by a mammal.
It was created by a snake.
Gary's great-grandmother.
She wanted to make the city a place where all animals felt welcome.
So she invented her weather walls to help everyone.
She just needed an investor.
A partner.
But when my great-grandfather saw what her idea could be worth, he plotted to steal her plans for himself.
So he committed a murder.
His own maid.
And framed Gary's great-grandmother.
And because she was a snake, everyone believed his lie.
Soon, no reptiles were welcome.
And over time, my great-grandfather buried the reptile neighborhood in snow.
And he died, believing no one could ever uncover his crimes.
But he was wrong.
Her original patent was saved.
That's what you're looking for.
She hid it in her home.
Find her home.
Find her a patent.
We just didn't know where her home was buried until now.
My family's land?
But under all...
Under all that snow, how are we gonna find it?
Wait, clock tower.
Her neighborhood, the reptile neighborhood, had a clock tower.
It lights up like a beacon.
If it wasn't fully buried, maybe we could see it.
Follow it to her home.
Except my great-grandfather turned off the power.
But we have the plans that show us how to turn it back on.
The power switch to her whole neighborhood was in.
The original control room.
Right.
And where is it?
Inside the oldest wall of the city.
The Desert Tundra Town Weather Wall.
We get inside, turn on that switch, light the clock tower, and we find her house.
We find her patent.
And my family is finally coming home.
We will succeed, Judy Hawks.
We shall succeed!
I found him.
Get me Hogbottom.
It's Nicholas Wild!
Big time cop, huh?
I'll see you at the lunch table.
I'm gonna toy your tail in a knot.
Hogbottom?
What are you looking at, butthead?
This is a mistake.
It's a setup.
It's the Lynxes.
Listen to me.
Please.
I know we have had our differences, right?
But I've always respected you.
You don't respect anyone.
Fun, it's Milton Lynxley.
He's got the redest location.
Whatever he says, it's a lie, Hogbottom.
Hogbottom, listen to me.
Nicholas, why?
What are the chances?
You know, this is my first time in prison, and I gotta say, their food is on point.
How are you even here?
Destiny.
Plus an arrest.
But it looks like Judith got away.
Was that decision mutual?
Oh.
Since in trouble in paradise.
Want to talk about it?
What I want is to get out of here.
Right, your big plan.
Lay low on Outback Island sipping piña koalas.
Except you can't trust koalas because they got four thumbs.
Did a whole episode about it on my podcast.
It was called They Got Four Thumbs.
But you know what?
Lisa ain't platypuses.
Wait, can you just, can you please just let me concentrate?
Roger that.
Just talk to me, dude.
What was the last thing she said to you?
She, um, she said maybe we are too different.
And what did you say before that?
I said the case isn't worth dying for.
Like, uh, like, you know, it isn't worth her dying for because solitary animals like me don't have real friends.
And I d I don't want to lose her.
I just.
I don't know how to say that.
You know what, bud?
I think you just did.
Wait, how'd you do that?
Well, I open my arms, put them around you, and then I squeezed.
It's called a hug.
Do foxes not have hugs?
Oh, the lock.
Yeah, that's beef 101.
The rabbits and dad of jeans!
Roll it!
Roll out!
Your partner needs you, and Nibble's maplestick is gonna get you to her!
Hey, it's the fox, dad!
And the woodchuck!
Woodchuck, I'm a beaver!
Call me that again!
Oh, Nicholas!
I hope you like my new home.
I wove it with my own wool.
We need wheels.
No, no.
No, no, no, no.
I'm sorry.
I do not think we can get to Judy in time to help.
Unless...
You happen to know the fastest driver in the history of Zootopia?
100-yard dash.
Partners in trouble need to get across town.
Ignore the laws.
No!
Problem!
Let's hit it!
Glad you're here.
I gotta tell you, I'm not convinced a sloth is our most reliable turn on the clock tower and light the way to your great-grandma's home so we can find her patent.
We need to reach the power control room through here.
But we have to move quickly or we're never going to...
We shall succeed to the ops.
Look, Gary, if we don't overprepare, we're underprepared, and I don't...
My family's been trying to prove we're not what everyone thinks for a hundred years.
But even this close, they never want me to put the weight of the world on my shoulders.
Because I don't have any shoulders.
This is.
We shall succeed.
I got you, habit.
I cannot help Judy if I don't know where she is, which is why I need you to get on Paul's computer and track Hot Bottom.
You are an escaped fugitive.
I could get fired for even talking to you.
They're gonna put her to sleep.
Do it, okay?
Did you try restarting it?
Mm-hmm.
Have you tried not being an idiot?
Hey, Paul.
I got you some doughnuts.
Oh, no.
Thanks, Paulhauser.
Plawhauser, location.
Oh, no.
I think we're gonna have to go through the festival.
Festival?
The phone's the first thing they track.
Go!
Hauser!
I am working on it!
Got it!
Great, great, great!
What festival is this?
We are with you, beauty hops.
We meet again, zebra.
You're coming!
She's gone for the dog!
We're out of time!
I got it!
Desert Tundra Town, weather wall access door!
Desert Tundra Town!
Weather wall access door!
Hurry!
What is in that wall?
A para control room.
But for like some old part of Tundra Town.
I know what they're doing.
They'll ruin us!
No more tranquilizers!
Put them down!
Sir!
Put them down now!
Take the shot!
Do it!
Sorry, not the switch.
No, no, no, no, not these.
It would be uh older.
Can you see it?
Did we turn on the clock tower?
There it's there.
We did it.
We can find the original patent.
Nick the door.
It's locked with.
How did it lock?
Nibbles!
Open it!
Thang door stuck on me!
Sorry.
Last case, there was kind of a twist.
I know.
Oh, my gosh.
I really...
Oh, my heart is pounding.
Oh, I thought you knew.
I thought you knew.
Sorry, partner.
Hate to leave you out in the cold, but I'm gonna.
Please don't be mad at me.
But, I mean, you get it.
We've always been on the same page.
Me and you, underdogs, right?
You gotta prove you're as good as everyone else.
That you belong.
I know it's messed up, but this is my chance.
I have to take it.
Because when I get to his great-grandma's home, and I burn the original patent, I'll finally be something in my family.
And I'll finally belong to.
Judy!
No loose ends.
Bye, partner.
Bye, Judy Hopps.
Partner, please.
You can't be different than your family.
I don't want to be different.
Nick, Judy.
Judy, Nibbles, do you see her?
No, nothing yet.
Judy, we shall succeed to the hardest.
It's okay.
Judy's happy.
She needs to find that.
Permission to hug We're gonna save you and save your friend Judy!
He's gonna eat that rabbit!
No, I'm waiting!
I'm saving her!
I'm gonna get her to empty then!
Where is she?
She didn't make it, but with snake bites, you go fast.
You'll see.
Agree to disagree.
I don't care.
What I care about is you.
I care about you.
I didn't say it.
I should have said it.
I didn't because I am an emotionally insecure source of your discomfort.
I was not good at expressing his feelings.
Probably because I've been on my own my whole life.
It's not an excuse.
It's just why instead of telling you that you're the best thing that ever happened.
to me, I make jokes about your ears, and I tell you that you try too hard.
When you know, the truth is, I just don't want you to get hurt because no one else in the world matters more to me than you do.
I do try too hard because deep down I'm afraid that I am what everyone thinks I am, and I suppress my discomfort because I'm worried it makes me look weak, and I want to be strong, and I think I'm failing all the time.
And I only take what you say personally because you're the only one in my life who ever believed in me, even when I don't even believe in myself.
And I should have told you that, but no one else in the world matters to me more than you do either.
I have unresolved childhood trauma that I refuse to discuss because being vulnerable scares me.
I make dangerous choices because I have an unhealthy but hero competition.
I didn't join the ZPD because I wanted to be a cop.
I joined because I always wanted to be part of a pack.
And the thought of losing you scares me because you're my pack.
I should never have left you.
And I do need a herd of therapy animals.
And I should have told you that you are the only partner I would ever want because you're my fluffle.
Um, that's a bunch of rabbits.
Now that is what we call an overshare.
I'm alive, by the way.
I made it.
Oh, also, that guy's still alive.
He's gonna get to the lost reptile neighborhood, find Gary's great-grandma's patents, and destroy it.
Yeah, I've got no idea what that means or who Gary is, but let's go!
Hops and wild.
Wild and hops.
And limboo's a Gary.
He's Gary.
Whoa, whoa.
Thank you.
It's for the snake.
He's cold.
No fur on him.
You!
You don't belong in this family.
You will never belong in this family.
Wait, wait, wait.
I wasn't working with them.
I was helping us.
I know where the reptile neighborhood is buried.
Where to find the real patent that proves that snakes invented the walls.
I'm gonna destroy it.
For the family.
For you, daddy.
You want to keep your job.
You say nothing.
You!
Maybe you are a Linksley.
Take me to the patent.
Takes a threesome to be some, but a four-way to bust your doorway.
Get to the patent!
Destroy it!
No!
We got this!
Hey, Whiskers!
You're done!
Harton McCity!
Uh-oh!
That's a turn!
Hey!
Ron Wind Dancer!
You want to be a hero?
Or just play one on TV?
I go left and and you go right?
Uh, yeah.
Or yes, I am.
We're gonna set it.
I'll destroy the package.
It's called an arrest, sweetheart.
Boom.
No one will believe you over us.
We've always been better than you, and we always will be.
Nothing you do matters.
Well, it matters to him.
Shall we?
I'm gonna burn it all to the ground.
I'm a real pig sleeve.
That'll do, pig.
That'll do.
Astonishing news today.
After officers Judy Hawks and Nicholas Wilde, along with a pit viper and a beaver, foiled another major conspiracy by revealing the true inventor of the city's weather walls.
was a snake.
Now, disgraceful Linksley family were revealed to have stolen the original plant and coveted for decades.
You have not heard the last of Melton.
Their Tundra Town expansion now officially canceled.
Some are calling you the dream team.
How did you do it?
Uh, well, there's a lot of different animals out there, and sometimes we start to look at all the little reasons that we're not the same.
And it makes us worry.
But maybe if we just talk to each other, if we just tried to understand one another, we would see that our differences don't really make any difference at all.
Maybe we'd even see that what makes me, me, and you, you, can make us even stronger.
And with hard work, you're going to get to that by year two.
Zebros.
Actually, my name is Gene.
My name is also Gene.
Zebros!
Kids, get off the stake.
How's everybody doing?
Wait a second.
This is my family.
Permission to hug.
I'm gonna get that back.
I'll get it back to you after our next decade.
There's gonna be another case, huh?
Of course.
Because when you broke out of jail, you also released 200 highly dangerous prisoners.
Any idea where you want to start?
One-way ticket to Outback Island, please.
First class.
Very nice.
Oh, and remember, if you're happy with our service, please be sure to leave us or thumbs up.
Oh, I will.
Harps and Wild.
Wild and cabbage patch.
Come on, get on up.
We're wild and we can't be damned.
And we're turning the floor into a zoo.
We live in a crazy world, caught up in a bad phrase.
Come and be jungle bad.
Sometimes a bad place.
It's you and me, you know, wild face.
Give it up, bubble baby.
Maybe it's your enemy.
Times to cool down.
Deanie was thinking fine.
What do we do now?
Talk about finding out.
Sometimes it's hard to come back.
But when it comes to us, it's a good time.
Only reason we are here is to set up.
And the place we're running, welcome again.
I'm a tip of this moment.
I'll take you back.
Baby, I'll take you back.
Come on, keep it up.
It's funny if you're down to play.
And we're turning the floor into a zoo.
Come on, keep it up.
We're wild and we can't be tense.
And we're turning the floor into a zoo.
Come on, keep it up.
It's funny if you're down to play.
And we're turning the floor into a zoo.
Love your partner.
Hey, buddy, you gotta keep playing that all night.
Labor alone, she's proud of herself, but still, this sort of allegations.
You shut up!
Hey, buddy, what's next we do?
Uh, we're investigating a rabbit who strangled her neighbor.
You offended her!
Good night!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm